Inventory of the Virginia B. Haughwout Papers 1951-1955
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Virginia B. Haughwout Papers, 1951-1955.
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Mss. 1997.17
ca. 75 items.
Correspondence concerning the construction of a building on the property owned by Virginia B. Haughwout on Duke of Gloucester Street, Williamsburg, Virginia. Includes architectural drawings and photographs.
Robert T. Armistead,; Kenneth Chorley,; Virginia B. Haughwout.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
Acc. No. 1997.17; Gift: ca. 75 items, 11 April 1997.
Scope and Content Information
Correspondence and legal papers, 1951-1955, of Mrs. Virginia B. Haughwout of Williamsburg, Virginia., about the construction of a Virginia Gazette building on her property on the Duke of Gloucester Street. Correspondence is chiefly with her lawyer Robert T. Armistead and Kenneth Chorley, President of the Colonial Williamsburg Foundation. Includes memorandum of argument on behalf of Colonial Williamsburg, Inc., prepared by the firm of Hunton, Williams, Gay, Moore & Powell, 6 June 1955, entitled Virginia B. Haughwout v. Board of Zoning Appeals of the City of Williamsburg, Virginia. Also includes architectural drawings and photographs.
Arrangement
Organization
This collection is arranged into 3 series. Series 1 contains papers; Series 2 contains architectural drawings; and Series 3 contains photographs.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Controlled Access Terms
Index Terms
Persons:
Armistead, Robert T.
Subjects:
Williamsburg (Va.)-- History--20th century.
Contents List
  Series 1: Papers
- Papers, 1951-1955. (Folder 1-9)
  - Papers, 1951. (Folder 1)
  - Papers, 1952. (Folder 2)
  - Papers, 1953. (Folder 3)
  - Papers, January-June 1954. (Folder 4)
  - Papers, July-December 1954. (Folder 5)
  - Papers, January-May 1955. (Folder 6)
  - Papers, June 1955. (Folder 7)
  - Papers, July-December 1955. (Folder 8)
  - Papers, n.d. (Folder 9)
  Series 2: Architectural Drawings
- Architectural drawings, 1951-1955. (Folder 10)
  Series 3: Photographs
- Photographs, 1951-1955. (Folder 11)